This project is a Java-based implementation of Wordle. The user has six attempts to guess a five-letter word. Feedback is provided each guess:

Green: Correct letter in correct position

Yellow: Correct letter in wrong position

Gray: Letter not in the word

The project features a GUI built with Swing, dynamically updating word boxes, a QWERTY keyboard info interface, and data loaded from a text file containing words used in the Wordle.

------------------------------------------

How to Run:

Open terminal in project root and run:

Powershell:

"./gradlew.bat run"

Command Prompt:

"gradlew.bat run"

Or just run the included "Wordle_Run.bat"

-------------------------------------------